If he gets knocked down
I won’t carry him
Regretting my choice
Not bury him
Should’ve wrung my neck
When you had the chance
Don’t understand
The dissonance
Cause it’s 2:13 and I think
I’m dead
I don’t wanna live
But I wake up
To a room inside my skin
And no one’s here
To give a fuck
About me
Or how I live
I barely did
I just get up
Despite the pain I’m in
I always win
I’ve always won
I thought I never had a chance
But I’ve been talking to my friends
This time it shows
I’m fucked I know
But I just can’t give up
They need me way to much
Need me to spill my guts
But it’s not enough
Think I need more love
But it never comes
Do I love myself?
Don’t think that’s enough
And I know I could compare myself
To all the ways it’s better alone
But I’d be dumb as fuck to think that I believed
That I’m worth anything more
Cause it’s 2:13 and I think
I’m dead
I don’t wanna live
But I wake up
To a room inside my skin
And no one’s here
To give a fuck
About me
Or how I live
I barely did
I just get up
Despite the pain I’m in
I always win
I’ve always won
Yeah I’ve always won
But I think I’m done
Oh I think I’m done
Yeah I think I’m done